Where am I?
Ow...
Are all of these bombs?
No way—
Why is this happening to me?
I'll give you the whole rundown.
You have to fight with
these bombs, called BIMs.
Fight whom, you ask?
The people standing next to you.
What is this?
This is fun!
It's so much fun!
No way.
I'm supposed to play BTOOOM! for real now?
Accept killing people as a game?
Taira-san, it's only been two minutes.
It's fine.
I like mine a little hard...
Lunchtime!
This is great!
I can feel it warming me up...
Attack
Delicious!
Was this really for the best?
Sakamoto-han...
Thank you so much.
I was so happy...
when you brought back that food.
Taira-san, you've already
said that plenty of times.
No, I could never say it enough.
I really am grateful.
When I hurt my leg,
you risked your life for me.
To me, you're a hero.
Not just anyone could've done that.
Thank you...
Thank you so much!
He's actually crying...
I don't think anyone has ever been
this grateful to me in my life.
I'm sure this was the right thing to do.
But why...
Why was I brought to this island?
I'm back!
Yukie, are you here?
Ryouta-kun?
Yukie! What are you doing?
Hisanobu-san,
I've done the worst thing a
parent could ever do...
B-But I had no choice...
Don't talk right now!
I'll call an ambulance!
I know that you got laid off.
You didn't want to worry us,
so you just suffered in silence.
But Ryouta...
Shut the hell up!
You're not even my real dad!
Don't act like you are!
Ryouta!
Name: Sakamoto Ryouta
I'm sorry, Hisanobu-san.
I'm sorry, Ryouta...
I'm so tired...
Wh-What's that?
A b-body?
He's really dead.
And he has no pants.
What's going on here?
There could be an enemy at
the top of that waterfall.
Let's get out of here, quickly.
W-Wait!
My leg's still hurt.
I can't move that fast...
This time, just leave me here.
Taira-san,
don't say something that sad ever again.
I couldn't leave you!
Sakamoto-han...
I'll go take a look.
You stay here and hide.
Two timers.
Two crackers.
And the three implosions and four
crackers I took from the kid.
Probably best not to let
Taira-san in on that yet.
Someone's waiting up ahead...
Should I use my radar?
No.
They'd see me, too.
It could be a murderer.
I need to get as close as I
can, and see for myself.
That makes two.
Oh yeah...
I need to hide.
The enemy's close...
Sakamoto-han,
be careful.
Don't throw up...
Don't throw it up!
Food is scarce here.
I need every bit of it to survive!
Swallow!
It's only been two days since
I arrived on this island...
I can't believe how much I
could change in two days.
And that corpse's chip is gone.
Whoever killed him is playing the game.
Fine, I'll use my radar!
Over there?
It must be someone evil,
who's killed lots of people...
It's that girl!
Did she kill him?
Stay away!
A BIM?!
That's the wrong way.
Is that a burning gas type?
In the game, that would
melt you upon contact.
This isn't good!
She lured me out.
She has so many BIMs.
Three... Four players' worth?
Did she take them from other
players she's killed?
She looks like a teenage girl,
but she's cruel!
W-Wait!
I don't want to fight.
I'm not going to play this game.
I just want to get off this island alive!
Please put down your BIMs,
and listen to me!
Is she the type who'd listen?
Tyrannos Japan, the guys who made
the game, are the bad guys here.
It's stupid to kill each other just
because they want us to!
Won't you help me,
so we can both get off this island?
If you don't want to help, I'll just leave.
Think about it, would you?
I-I guess I convinced her to relax.
Oh, good...
You tried to get me to drop my
guard so you could get close
and do something awful!
Men...
All men are my enemies!
W-Wait!
She's got a terrible arm...
Was that supposed to be aimed at me?
But she really did want to kill me.
Then...
He's too close!
A stun gun?
Blue eyes...
Blonde hair.
Are you a foreigner?
Do you understand me?
I can not speak—
Don't insult me!
I'm Japanese.
I just can't trust men!
Didn't you attack me, too?!
Wait!
You attacked me—
Shut up!
Crap!
It knocked her out?
What's her problem?
Hey, wake up.
Hey...
Honestly.
But this girl...
She smells good.
Hey, wake up.
I said wake up.
All men are my enemies!
I don't want her going nuts again.
I should take away her weapons.
It feels like I'm removing her panties...
But if I really did,
I bet she wouldn't notice.
She's cute...
No one's around.
That was close...
What was I thinking?
And he has no pants.
What's going on here?
So that's what happened...
She was attacked by that man here.
Want... want... I want!
You're awake?
You got hit with your own stun gun.
You'll be too numb to move for a while.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt you.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
A timer BIM?
She had a hidden one?!
Don't do it! Don't be stupid!
I won't let you rape me.
I'd rather die...
Men are just animals!
I'd rather die by my own hand
than be raped and killed
on this island.
Die while I'm still pure...
I have nowhere to return to, anyway!
I don't care if I die...
I don't care.
She was seriously going to kill herself.
That wasn't a bluff.
Just now, she actually threw away her life...
Drink up.
It's warm coffee.
Taira-san, that's...
No other choice...
We don't have any cups.
It's as good a cup as any.
I washed it, so don't worry.
Here.
You must've been through a lot...
But don't worry anymore.
We're with you.
We won't do anything weird.
I promise! We won't.
I decided I'd make it off
this island on my own,
without playing the game.
So I'd really like you to help us.
Let's escape together.
Thankfully, we have plenty of food.
And lots of bombs, too.
So there's nothing to be afraid of.
No.
Even if we get back,
there's no guarantee anything
will be waiting for us...
What do you mean?
People who knew each of us well
chose us to be sent here.
They picked us out as someone
they'd want to disappear.
Even if we went back to those
people, then what?
What do you mean?!
Do you mean our friends and
families have abandoned us?
I can't believe that!
I have a great relationship with my family.
They wouldn't want me to disappear!
I just mean they're people we know.
Have you done anything to someone that
would make them hate you recently?
C-Come to think of it...
I got in a big fight with a
customer last month...
How do you know this?
The two of us weren't told this!
Where did you hear it?
Where?
They told me.
We all picked you...
We all hope you disappear!
Someone chose us to disappear?
Then, that would go for
everyone on this island?
Taira-san?
That kid?
And me?
Someone chose me...
No way.
That can't be...
No!
My mom?
I don't have anywhere else to go.
I don't have anywhere...
What are you saying?!
You can't say that!
You have to live!
We need to survive and
escape this island...
Get back home!
Once we're back, we can work things out!
We can't give up!
What's wrong?
Something's there...
I-Is someone nearby?
I heard something!
Nothing?
But I can hear something getting closer.
Radar canceling?
But...
Wh-What are those?!
They aren't human...
Panthers?
Wolves?
The radar should respond!
Fire! We need more fire!
Get away from the forest!
What are you doing? Come on!
That's right.
That hit from the stun gun!
Come on, stand up! Hurry!
Th-These things are giant lizards!
You've gotta be kidding!
I was kind to my family,
but I was a monster at work...
It wouldn't surprise me if
any of them hated me.
This is karma...
Yes, this is my punishment.
Episode 6: Night of Sacrifice